{
    "subject": "resource/Almere_City_FC",
    "predicate": "ontology/league",
    "object": "resource/Eerste_Divisie",
    "human_readable": "Almere City FC plays in Eerste Divisie.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8703368902206421,
            "question": "What division does Almere City FC play in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7989760041236877,
            "question": "Which team plays in the Eerste Divisie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7951629161834717,
            "question": "Is Almere City FC a team in the Eredivisie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7873761653900146,
            "question": "Name a team that plays in the Eerste Divisie."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7790707945823669,
            "question": "Where does Almere City FC play its matches?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5674221515655518,
            "question": "In what league does Almere City FC compete?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5050078630447388,
            "question": "What league is Almere City FC currently part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46255338191986084,
            "question": "What is the name of the football league Almere City FC belongs to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35798072814941406,
            "question": "What is the level of competition for Almere City FC?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25697797536849976,
            "question": "Is the Eerste Divisie a higher or lower league than the Eredivisie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Almere City FC plays in Eerste Divisie.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7684_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the level of competition for Almere City FC?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7684_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the football league Almere City FC belongs to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7684_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What league is Almere City FC currently part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7684_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7684_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe query \"Almere City FC plays in Eerste Divisie\" is supported by the documents, which state that \"Almere City FC competes in the Eerste Divisie, the second-highest professional football league in the Netherlands.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}